<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Summarised Feed</title><link>http://example.com</link><description>Summaries of articles from another feed.</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:26:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Meta is making all Facebook videos reels</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688828/meta-facebook-videos-reels</link><description>- Meta is removing length restrictions for Facebook Reels, allowing videos longer than 90 seconds.
- In the coming months, all videos shared on Facebook will be converted into Reels, simplifying the sharing process.
- The Video tab on Facebook will be renamed to Reels, and the platform aims to promote Reels more prominently.
- These changes are part of Meta’s effort to make Facebook more influential culturally and to encourage Reels usage.
- The updates will be rolled out gradually to profiles and Pages worldwide, with Facebook still supporting a variety of video types.</description></item><item><title>Senate confirms Trump’s FCC pick, Olivia Trusty</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688824/olivia-trusty-fcc-senate-confirmation-trump</link><description>- The Senate confirmed Olivia Trusty, a Republican, to the Federal Communications Commission (FCC), restoring its quorum.
- Trusty's appointment shifts the FCC to a 2-1 Republican majority, potentially influencing the agency's policies.
- Democratic Senator Maria Cantwell expressed concerns about Trusty's nomination due to the Trump administration's broader actions and the lack of a Democratic nominee.
- The confirmation allows Republican Chair Brendan Carr to pursue a more conservative agenda, including deregulation and media policy changes.
- Some critics worry that Trusty's appointment could lead to increased partisan control over the FCC and media regulation.</description></item><item><title>Trump is giving TikTok another ban extension</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688252/tiktok-ban-trump-extension-deal</link><description>- The article discusses the US government's repeated extension of a deadline for TikTok to be sold or separated from its Chinese parent company, ByteDance, which now extends into mid-September.
- These extensions are intended to provide legal cover for US companies like Oracle and Apple that facilitate TikTok, but their legality is questionable since they are not officially codified into law.
- Despite negotiations earlier in the year, no deal has been finalized, and concerns remain about whether China would allow ByteDance to sell its core algorithm, which is central to TikTok's service.
- Lawmakers and officials have criticized the extensions as potentially illegal and risky for companies, with some warning that courts could challenge the legality if lawsuits are filed.
- Overall, there is uncertainty about how the US will enforce the TikTok ban and whether indefinite extensions or new deals will be approved.</description></item><item><title>Iran is going offline to prevent purported Israeli cyberattacks</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/politics/688875/iran-cutting-off-internet-israel-war</link><description>- Iran is intentionally slowing down its internet and plans to disconnect from the global internet entirely, citing a need to prevent cyberattacks during escalating tensions with Israel.
- The government has encouraged citizens to delete WhatsApp, claiming it is being used for spying by Israel, and has also blocked other messaging apps like Telegram.
- Internet outages are affecting basic services, with reports of reduced access to messaging, maps, and VPNs, and some cellular carriers going offline.
- The move is part of Iran's response amid increased cyberattacks on Israel, which have surged since the conflict began.
- Experts warn that the cyber conflict could spill over, potentially affecting US infrastructure if the conflict escalates further.</description></item><item><title>The best instant cameras you can buy right now</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/23133103/best-instant-cameras-fujifilm-polaroid-kodak</link><description>- The article reviews and compares popular instant cameras from brands like Fujifilm, Polaroid, Kodak, Leica, and Canon, focusing on their features, ease of use, and photo quality.
- The Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 is recommended as the best all-around instant camera for most people due to its affordability, simple operation, and decent image quality.
- Hybrid cameras like the Fujifilm Instax Mini Evo and Leica Sofort 2 offer more creative controls, app integration, and the ability to print from smartphones, but tend to be more expensive.
- Classic Polaroid cameras such as the Polaroid Now Plus and Polaroid Go provide vintage-style photos with a retro design, though they can be bulky, and their photos may struggle in low-light conditions.
- Film costs and availability vary across models, influencing the total cost of ownership, with some cameras using more affordable or more readily available film options.</description></item></channel></rss>