<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Summarised Feed</title><link>http://example.com</link><description>Summaries of articles from another feed.</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:57:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Meta is making all Facebook videos reels</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688828/meta-facebook-videos-reels</link><description>- Meta is changing how videos are shared on Facebook, moving towards making all videos appear as Reels in the future.  
- The company plans to remove the current 90-second limit for Facebook Reels and will rename the Video tab to Reels.  
- These updates aim to make creating, sharing, and discovering Reels easier on Facebook, with a gradual rollout worldwide over the coming months.  
- Despite the changes, Facebook will still support a variety of video types and lengths, with personalized recommendations remaining unaffected.  
- The move aligns with Meta's broader strategy to boost Reels on its platforms and increase Facebook's cultural influence.</description></item><item><title>Senate confirms Trump’s FCC pick, Olivia Trusty</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688824/olivia-trusty-fcc-senate-confirmation-trump</link><description>- The Senate confirmed Olivia Trusty, a Republican, to the FCC, restoring its quorum and allowing it to function fully.  
- Trusty's appointment adds to a Republican majority on the FCC, with two seats still vacant.  
- Some Democrats expressed concern about her nomination due to broader concerns about the Trump administration's approach to independent agencies.  
- Her confirmation is viewed as enabling the current FCC Chair Brendan Carr to pursue a more deregulatory and partisan agenda.  
- The article notes ongoing political tensions and concerns about the potential for increased partisanship at the FCC.</description></item><item><title>Trump is giving TikTok another ban extension</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688252/tiktok-ban-trump-extension-deal</link><description>- The article discusses the US government's repeated extension of the deadline for TikTok to sell its US operations or face a ban, with President Trump signing a 90-day extension to mid-September.
- These extensions are seen as legally questionable because they are not formally part of law, and critics argue they provide shaky legal cover for companies like Oracle and Apple that keep TikTok accessible.
- Despite ongoing trade tensions, no new deal has been reached between TikTok's parent company ByteDance and US companies, and there are concerns about whether China would permit sale of TikTok's algorithm.
- Lawmakers from both parties have criticized the extensions as unlawful and warned that they could expose US service providers to legal risks.
- Some legal actions and shareholder lawsuits have been filed related to the enforcement and legality of these extensions, but no court has yet intervened.</description></item><item><title>Iran is going offline to prevent purported Israeli cyberattacks</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/politics/688875/iran-cutting-off-internet-israel-war</link><description>- Iran is intentionally reducing its own internet access and plans to disconnect from the global internet to limit Israel’s cyber capabilities amid ongoing conflict.  
- The government has asked citizens to delete WhatsApp, claiming it has been used for spying, and has blocked other messaging apps like Telegram.  
- Reports indicate widespread internet outages and reduced access to messaging services, affecting civilians' ability to communicate.  
- The move is part of Iran’s response to escalating tensions with Israel, which has also seen a surge in cyberattacks targeting Israel.  
- Experts warn that these cyber activities could lead to broader cyber warfare and potential spillover effects on other countries, including the US.</description></item><item><title>The best instant cameras you can buy right now</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/23133103/best-instant-cameras-fujifilm-polaroid-kodak</link><description>- The article reviews various instant cameras from brands like Fujifilm, Polaroid, Kodak, Leica, and Canon, focusing on their features, image quality, ease of use, and price.
- The Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 is recommended as the best option for most people due to its good balance of print quality, simplicity, and affordability.
- Hybrid models like the Fujifilm Instax Mini Evo and Kodak Mini Shot 3 Retro offer more creative controls, app connectivity, and the ability to print from smartphones, but tend to be more expensive and complex.
- Vintage-style models like the Polaroid Now Plus and Polaroid Go provide nostalgic appeal with simple operation, but may have limitations in low-light conditions and image sharpness.
- The article emphasizes that instant cameras produce characteristic soft, imperfect images, and choosing the right model depends on your budget, desired features, and how much creative control you want.</description></item></channel></rss>