<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Summarised Feed</title><link>http://example.com</link><description>Summaries of articles from another feed.</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Meta is making all Facebook videos reels</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688828/meta-facebook-videos-reels</link><description>- Meta is changing how videos are shared on Facebook by making all videos appear as Reels in the future.  
- Length restrictions for Facebook Reels will be removed, allowing videos longer than the current 90 seconds.  
- The Video tab on Facebook will be renamed to Reels tab to emphasize the focus on short videos.  
- These updates aim to make creating, sharing, and discovering Reels easier and more consistent across Facebook.  
- The changes are part of Meta’s broader effort to boost Facebook’s influence and focus more on video content, similar to Reels on Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Senate confirms Trump’s FCC pick, Olivia Trusty</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688824/olivia-trusty-fcc-senate-confirmation-trump</link><description>- The Senate confirmed Olivia Trusty, a Republican, to the Federal Communications Commission (FCC), restoring a quorum to the agency.  
- Trusty's appointment brings the FCC to a 2-1 Republican majority, allowing more partisan policy decisions.  
- The confirmation faced some opposition from Democrats, notably Senator Maria Cantwell, due to concerns about the Trump administration's actions and the lack of a Democratic nominee.  
- Trusty has a background working for Senator Roger Wicker and is seen as aligned with the Trump administration's agenda.  
- Critics worry that her appointment could lead to a more partisan FCC, potentially impacting media regulation and independence.</description></item><item><title>Trump is giving TikTok another ban extension</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688252/tiktok-ban-trump-extension-deal</link><description>- The article discusses the US government's repeated extensions of the deadline for TikTok to either divest from its Chinese parent company or face a potential ban in the United States.
- President Trump announced a 90-day extension of the deadline, aiming to give time for a deal that would ensure US user data is secure, but legal experts and lawmakers question the legality of these extensions.
- The extensions are not officially backed by law, leading to concerns that service providers like Apple and Google could face legal penalties for continuing to host TikTok.
- Past negotiations for a sale or deal involving TikTok and US companies, such as Oracle, have fallen through, and there is uncertainty about whether China would permit the sale of TikTok’s algorithm.
- Some lawmakers and stakeholders warn that Trump’s repeated extensions may be illegal and create legal risks, but so far, no lawsuits have successfully challenged the extensions.</description></item><item><title>Iran is going offline to prevent purported Israeli cyberattacks</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/politics/688875/iran-cutting-off-internet-israel-war</link><description>- Iran is intentionally slowing down its internet and planning to disconnect from the global internet entirely, citing security concerns amidst escalating conflict with Israel.  
- The government has urged citizens to delete WhatsApp and has restricted access to messaging apps like Telegram, claiming they are used for spying, though these claims lack evidence.  
- Reports indicate significant internet outages in Iran, with some cellular carriers going offline and VPN access becoming more difficult.  
- The conflict has led to a surge in cyberattacks against Israel, and experts warn that US companies and infrastructure could be at risk if the situation escalates.  
- The article focuses on Iran’s internet restrictions and cyber activities related to the ongoing war with Israel.</description></item><item><title>The best instant cameras you can buy right now</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/23133103/best-instant-cameras-fujifilm-polaroid-kodak</link><description>- The article reviews various instant cameras, focusing on their features, image quality, ease of use, and price to help readers choose the best one for their needs.
- The Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 is recommended as the best overall for most people due to its good photo quality, simplicity, and affordability.
- Other notable models include the Fujifilm Instax Mini Evo (hybrid with creative controls and app support), Polaroid Now Plus and Polaroid Go (vintage style with modern features), and Kodak Mini Shot 3 Retro (fun with smartphone printing).
- The article highlights that instant cameras typically produce lower-quality photos than digital cameras, especially in low light, but offer a nostalgic and tactile photography experience.
- Film costs, compatibility, and additional features like filters or creative modes vary across models and should be considered when choosing an instant camera.</description></item></channel></rss>