<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Summarised Feed</title><link>http://example.com</link><description>Summaries of articles from another feed.</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 01:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Meta is making all Facebook videos reels</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688828/meta-facebook-videos-reels</link><description>- Meta is changing how videos are shared on Facebook, with all videos soon being shared as Reels.  
- The company will remove the current 90-second limit for Facebook Reels, allowing longer videos.  
- The existing Video tab will be renamed to Reels tab on Facebook.  
- These updates aim to make creating, sharing, and discovering Reels easier, aligning with Meta's goal to boost Facebook's cultural influence.  
- The changes will be rolled out gradually worldwide over the coming months.</description></item><item><title>Senate confirms Trump’s FCC pick, Olivia Trusty</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688824/olivia-trusty-fcc-senate-confirmation-trump</link><description>- The Senate confirmed Olivia Trusty, a Republican, to the Federal Communications Commission (FCC), restoring the agency's quorum.  
- Trusty's confirmation was 53-45, with only one Democrat, Sen. Fetterman, voting in her favor.  
- Her appointment gives the FCC a 2-1 Republican majority, which could influence the agency’s future policies.  
- Some Democrats expressed concerns about the Trump administration’s influence and the lack of a Democratic nominee.  
- The article notes ongoing partisan tensions and potential shifts in media regulation as a result of the new FCC composition.</description></item><item><title>Trump is giving TikTok another ban extension</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688252/tiktok-ban-trump-extension-deal</link><description>- The article discusses the US government's repeated extension of the deadline for TikTok to sell its US operations or face a ban, with President Trump extending it for 90 days each time.
- These extensions are intended to give US companies like Oracle and Apple legal cover to continue operating TikTok, but their legality is questionable since they are not formally codified into law.
- There have been ongoing efforts to reach a deal for TikTok to be sold or separated from its Chinese parent company, but political and legal challenges remain, especially regarding the transfer of TikTok’s algorithm.
- Some lawmakers and officials have criticized the extensions as potentially illegal and risky for US service providers, who could face fines if they keep TikTok online after the deadline.
- So far, no legal actions have been taken to challenge the extensions, but some shareholders and lawmakers have expressed concerns about the legality and implications of the ongoing delays.</description></item><item><title>Iran is going offline to prevent purported Israeli cyberattacks</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/politics/688875/iran-cutting-off-internet-israel-war</link><description>- Iran is intentionally throttling its citizens' internet access and plans to disconnect from the global internet entirely to limit Israel’s cyber capabilities amid ongoing conflict.
- The government claims the internet slowdown is temporary and aimed at preventing cyberattacks, but civilians report losing access to messaging apps, maps, and other services.
- Iran has urged people to delete WhatsApp, accusing the app of espionage, while also blocking other messaging platforms like Telegram.
- The internet outages coincide with a rise in cyberattacks on Israel, and experts warn that the conflict could lead to broader cyberwarfare involving other countries, including the US.
- The article notes that Iran’s internal internet may still be accessible, but overall connectivity is significantly reduced.</description></item><item><title>The best instant cameras you can buy right now</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/23133103/best-instant-cameras-fujifilm-polaroid-kodak</link><description>The article discusses the best instant cameras available, highlighting their features, usability, and image quality. Key points include:

- Instant cameras offer a nostalgic and tactile photography experience, with images that have a unique, imperfect charm compared to digital photos.
- The Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 is recommended as the best overall choice for most users due to its ease of use, good print quality, and affordability.
- Hybrid models like Fujifilm’s Instax Mini Evo, Polaroid Now Plus, and Kodak Mini Shot 3 Retro provide additional creative features, app connectivity, and the ability to print from smartphones.
- Print quality varies across models, with some cameras struggling in low-light conditions or producing less sharp images, and film costs can add up quickly.
- More advanced or larger-format cameras, such as the Fujifilm Instax Mini 99 or Wide Evo Hybrid, cater to enthusiasts but are generally more expensive and complex to operate.</description></item></channel></rss>