<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>My Summarised Feed</title><link>http://example.com</link><description>Summaries of articles from another feed.</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:39:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Meta is making all Facebook videos reels</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688828/meta-facebook-videos-reels</link><description>- Meta is changing how videos are shared on Facebook, moving towards making all videos appear as Reels in the future.  
- The company will remove the current 90-second limit for Facebook Reels, allowing longer videos.  
- The Video tab on Facebook will be renamed to the Reels tab to reflect this focus.  
- These updates aim to make it easier for users to create, share, and discover Reels on Facebook.  
- The changes are part of Meta's broader strategy to boost video content and increase Facebook's cultural influence.</description></item><item><title>Senate confirms Trump’s FCC pick, Olivia Trusty</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688824/olivia-trusty-fcc-senate-confirmation-trump</link><description>- The Senate confirmed Olivia Trusty, a Republican, to the Federal Communications Commission (FCC), restoring a quorum at the agency.  
- Trusty's appointment gives the FCC a 2-1 Republican majority, enabling the chair to push forward his agenda.  
- Some Democrats, like Maria Cantwell, expressed concerns about Trusty's nomination, citing the Trump administration’s broader actions and partisan issues.  
- The confirmation process highlighted concerns over potential partisan shifts and the future direction of media and communications policies.  
- The article notes that two FCC seats remain vacant, with additional nominations pending from President Trump.</description></item><item><title>Trump is giving TikTok another ban extension</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/news/688252/tiktok-ban-trump-extension-deal</link><description>- The article discusses the US government's repeated extensions of a deadline for TikTok to be sold or spun off from its Chinese parent company, ByteDance, with the latest extension set for mid-September.  
- These extensions are intended to provide legal cover for US companies like Oracle and Apple that host or facilitate access to TikTok, but their legality is questionable because they are not officially codified into law.  
- There has been no recent progress on a deal to sell TikTok’s algorithm or operations, and concerns remain about whether China would allow the sale of the algorithm that powers TikTok’s recommendations.  
- Lawmakers and officials have criticized the extensions as potentially illegal and warned that they could expose US companies to legal risks, though no one has yet challenged the extensions in court.  
- The main topic is the ongoing US debate and legal uncertainty over TikTok’s future and the legality of the government’s actions to restrict its operations in the US.</description></item><item><title>Iran is going offline to prevent purported Israeli cyberattacks</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/politics/688875/iran-cutting-off-internet-israel-war</link><description>- Iran is intentionally reducing its citizens' internet access by throttling bandwidth and planning to disconnect from the global internet, citing cybersecurity concerns amid ongoing conflict with Israel.  
- The Iranian government has urged people to delete WhatsApp, claiming it is used for spying by Israel, although these claims lack evidence; other messaging apps like Telegram are also blocked.  
- Reports indicate significant internet outages in Iran, including reduced access to messaging services, maps, and VPNs, with some services going completely offline.  
- The conflict has led to a sharp rise in cyberattacks against Israel, and experts warn that US companies and infrastructure could be at risk if the conflict escalates further.  
- The article notes that the government continues to provide limited access through state-operated internet services, even as overall connectivity declines.</description></item><item><title>The best instant cameras you can buy right now</title><link>https://www.theverge.com/23133103/best-instant-cameras-fujifilm-polaroid-kodak</link><description>- The article reviews various instant cameras, highlighting their features, image quality, ease of use, and price to help readers choose the best one for their needs.
- The Fujifilm Instax Mini 12 is recommended as the best overall for most people due to its good print quality, simplicity, and affordability.
- Other notable models include the Fujifilm Instax Mini Evo, which offers creative controls and smartphone printing, and the Polaroid Now Plus, known for its vintage style and modern features.
- The article discusses the differences between hybrid cameras that print smartphone photos and traditional film-based instant cameras, emphasizing considerations like film cost and photo quality.
- Overall, the choice depends on user preferences for photo style, creative features, portability, and budget, with several options suited for beginners, children, or more advanced users.</description></item></channel></rss>